https://www.linnareacu.org/privacy-policy/

Effective Thursday, November 19, our lobbies will be closed due to the increased number of COVID-19 cases in our community. We will continue to offer drive-through services. Learn more about our response to COVID-19. >>PersonalChecking Checking Account TypesApply For MembershipDebit Cards / ATMOverdraft ServicesDirect DepositFee ScheduleOrder ChecksChecking Deposit RatesSavings Savings Account TypesApply For MembershipHealth Savings Account (HSA)Savings BondsMoney Market AccountSavings Deposit RatesLoans Auto Loans Auto Loan RatesRecreational Vehicle (RV) LoansMortgage Loans Mortgage Loan TypesMortgage Loan RatesMortgage GlossaryMortgage ApplicationHome Equity Loans Home Equity Loan RatesHome Equity Line of Credit (HELOC) Home Equity Loan RatesPersonal LoansDebt ConsolidationStudent LoansAutomatic Deductions & PaymentsNMLS NumbersCredit Cards Apply for a Credit CardCredit Card RatesTransfer Your BalanceInvesting IRAs (Individual Retirement Accounts)CDs (Certificates of Deposit)Insurance TruStage® Auto & Home Insurance ProgramTruStage® Life InsuranceTruStage® AD&D InsuranceGuaranteed Auto ProtectionDepreciation ProtectionExtended Warranty InsuranceCredit Life InsuranceCredit Disability InsuranceMember Services Wire TransfersIn-Branch Member Services Cashier’s ChecksNotary ServicesSignature GuaranteeCoin MachinesNight Drop BoxSafe Deposit BoxesStatement CopiesDigital Services Online Banking Online Banking Tutorial VideosIdentity Verification and Trusted Devices FAQMobile Banking Mobile Banking Tutorial VideosIdentity Verification and Trusted Devices FAQMobile Deposit Mobile Deposit FAQDigital Wallets Apple PayGoogle PaySamsung PayShopPING Card ProtectionBill Payer PopmoneyeStatementsART (Audio Response Teller)BusinessBusiness Checking Business Checking Account TypesBusiness Fee ScheduleOrder Business ChecksBusiness Checking Deposit RatesBusiness Savings Business Health Savings Account (HSA)Business Money Market AccountBusiness Loans Small Business LoansCommercial LoansBusiness ServicesLearnAuto Buying a CarGetting Your First CarBudgeting & Saving How to Keep from Overspending OnlineHow to Save MoneyMake a BudgetCareer & Education Maximizing Your New Job BenefitsPlanning for CollegeChecking Balancing Your CheckbookGetting Your First Checking AccountCredit & Debt Get Your Free Credit ReportGetting Your First Credit CardGetting Your First LoanImprove Your CreditManage DebtUsing CreditYour Credit ScoreHome & Mortgage Buying a HomeBuying a Second HomeHome Repair Emergency FundWhat You Need for Moving DayInsurance Choosing InsuranceLife, Family & Retirement Financial Planning for a Health EmergencyFinancial Unity in MarriageGetting MarriedHow to Deal with StressHow to Focus on Personal GrowthLosing a Loved OneMastering Self-TalkPlanning for a FamilyPlanning for RetirementPlanning a VacationWriting a WillSecurity & Fraud Protection Avoiding Identity Theft & FraudBeware of Tax ScamsRecognizing Phishing ScamsShop Online SafelyFinancial Calculators Mortgage Calculators Mortgage CalculatorAdjustable Rate Mortgage CalculatorMortgage Qualifier CalculatorHome Rent vs. Buy CalculatorMortgage Payoff CalculatorMortgage Refinance CalculatorHome Equity Line of Credit CalculatorAuto Calculators Auto LoanAuto Loan Early Payoff CalculatorDealer Financing vs. Credit Union FinancingLease vs BuyLoan Calculators Loan CalculatorHome Equity Line of CreditDebt ConsolidationLoan & Credit Line Tax SavingsSavings Calculators Benefit of Spending LessCD (Certificate of Deposit)College SavingsCool Million CalculatorEmergency Savings CalculatorSavings CalculatorSavings GoalsHealth Savings Account (HSA)Personal Finance Calculators Checkbook Balancing CalculatorHome Budget AnalysisShould My Spouse Work?Student Budget CalculatorCredit & Debt Calculators Accelerated Debt PayoffCredit Card PayoffHome Equity Debt ConsolidationHow Much Do You Owe?Personal Debt ConsolidationRetirement Calculators 401(k) Savings401(k) Spend It or Save ItBeneficiary Required Minimum DistributionsRetirement IncomeRetirement Nest EggRetirement PlannerRoth IRATraditional IRAInsurance Calculators Life Insurance CalculatorLong Term Care Calculator
Search
Search for:
Online BankingRatesYou are leaving Linn Area Credit Union's website.Linn Area Credit Union does not provide, and is not responsible for, the product, service, website content, security, or privacy policy on any external third-party sites. Please keep this in mind when visiting external websites. Stop back soon!CancelOkayHome
Privacy PolicyFacts
What does Linn Area Credit Union do with your personal information?Why?Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.What?The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:Social Security NumberIncomePayment HistoryCredit HistoryAccount Balance(s)Credit ScoresWhen you are no longer our member, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.How?All financial companies need to share members’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their members’ personal information; the reasons Linn Area Credit Union chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.Reasons we can share your personal informationDoes Linn Area Credit Union share?Can you limit this sharing?For our everyday business purposes — such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus
Yes
NoFor our marketing purposes — to offer our products and services to you
Yes
NoFor joint marketing with other financial companies
Yes
NoFor our affiliates’ everyday business purposes — information about your transactions and experiences
No
We don't share.For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes — information about your creditworthiness
No
We don't share.For nonaffiliates to market to you
No
We don't share.
Questions?
Call (319) 892-7300 or toll free (800) 950-5228.Who we are
Who is providing this notice?Linn Area Credit Union3015 Blairs Ferry Road NECedar Rapids, IA 52402(319) 892-7300 or (800) 950-5228What we do
How does Linn Area Credit Union protect my personal information?To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings. These may include locked cabinets and security systems for our facilities; passwords and fire walls for our web sites; and having our employees ask for identification before processing your requests.
How does Linn Area Credit Union collect my personal information?We collect your personal information, for example, when you:open an accountapply for a loandeposit moneypay your billsuse your debit or credit cardWe also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing?Federal law gives you the right to limit onlysharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information about your creditworthinessaffiliates from using your information to market to yousharing for nonaffiliates to market to youState laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.Definitions
AffiliatesCompanies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial or nonfinancial companies. Linn Area Credit Union has no affiliates.
NonaffiliatesCompanies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial or nonfinancial companies. Linn Area Credit Union does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you.
Joint MarketingA formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.Our joint marketing partners include insurance companies. Log In     Enroll Today   Forgot Password?
LendingSavings
Credit Card
APR as low as
9.90%
Auto
APR as low as
2.90%
Personal Loan
0.65%View All Deposit RatesApply For Membership
Live ChatCategoriesA Fantastic Place to WorkAuto LoansBusiness CheckingBusiness LoansBusiness SavingsCheckingContestsCredit CardsEventsFinancial EducationHome Equity LoansInsuranceKirby Kids ClubLife HappensMortgage LoansOnline & Mobile ServicesOur Community Rocks!Personal LoansPromotionsRetirement & InvestmentsRV & Boat LoansSavingStudent LoansTeachers & EducationTipsWe Love Our Members!Young AdultsJoin our family! Apply for membershipYou'll be glad you did!Get a low new-car rate on every model yearOffer ends 12/31/20
Learn more
PersonalCheckingChecking Account TypesApply For MembershipDebit Cards / ATMOverdraft ServicesDirect DepositFee ScheduleOrder ChecksChecking Deposit RatesSavingsSavings Account TypesApply For MembershipHealth Savings Account (HSA)Savings BondsMoney Market AccountSavings Deposit RatesLoansAuto LoansAuto Loan RatesRecreational Vehicle (RV) LoansMortgage LoansMortgage Loan TypesMortgage RatesMortgage GlossaryApply for a Mortgage LoanHome Equity LoansHome Equity Loan RatesHome Equity Line of Credit (HELOC)Home Equity Loan RatesPersonal LoansDebt ConsolidationStudent LoansAutomatic Deductions & PaymentsNMLS NumbersCredit CardsApply For a Credit CardCredit Card RatesTransfer Your BalanceInvestingIRAs (Individual Retirement Accounts)CDs (Certificates of Deposit)InsuranceTruStage® Auto & Home Insurance ProgramTruStage® Life InsuranceGuaranteed Auto ProtectionDepreciation ProtectionExtended Warranty InsuranceTruStage® AD&D (Accidental Death & Dismemberment Insurance)Credit Life InsuranceCredit Disability InsuranceMember ServicesWire TransfersIn-Branch Member ServicesCashier’s ChecksNotary ServicesSignature GuaranteeCoin MachinesNight Drop BoxSafe Deposit BoxesStatement CopiesDigital ServicesOnline BankingOnline Banking Tutorial VideosMobile BankingMobile Banking Tutorial VideosMobile DepositMobile Deposit with Linn Area Credit Union FAQDigital WalletsApple PayGoogle PaySamsung PayShopPING Card ProtectionBill PayerPopmoneyeStatementsART (Audio Response Teller)BusinessBusiness CheckingBusiness Checking Account TypesBusiness Fee ScheduleOrder Business ChecksBusiness Checking Deposit RatesBusiness SavingsBusiness Health Savings Account (HSA)Business Money Market AccountBusiness LoansSmall Business LoansCommercial LoansBusiness ServicesLearnAutoBuying a CarGetting Your First CarBudgeting & SavingHow to Keep from Overspending OnlineHow to Save MoneyMake a BudgetCareer & EducationMaximizing Your New Job BenefitsPlanning for CollegeCheckingBalancing Your CheckbookGetting Your First Checking AccountCredit & DebtGet Your Free Credit ReportGetting Your First Credit CardGetting Your First LoanImprove Your CreditManage DebtUsing CreditYour Credit ScoreHome & MortgageBuying a HomeBuying a Second HomeHome Repair Emergency FundWhat You Need for Moving DayInsuranceChoosing InsuranceLife, Family & RetirementFinancial Planning for a Health EmergencyFinancial Unity in MarriageGetting MarriedHow to Deal with StressHow to Focus on Personal GrowthLosing a Loved OneMastering Self-TalkPlanning for a FamilyPlanning for RetirementPlanning a VacationWriting a WillSecurity & Fraud ProtectionAvoiding Identity Theft & FraudBeware of Tax ScamsRecognizing Phishing ScamsShop Online SafelyFinancial CalculatorsMortgage CalculatorsMortgage CalculatorAdjustable Rate Mortgage CalculatorMortgage Qualifier CalculatorHome Rent vs. Buy CalculatorMortgage Payoff CalculatorMortgage Refinance CalculatorHome Equity Line of Credit CalculatorAuto CalculatorsAuto LoanAuto Loan Early Payoff CalculatorDealer Financing vs. Credit Union FinancingLease vs BuyLoan CalculatorsLoan CalculatorHome Equity Line of CreditDebt ConsolidationLoan & Credit Line Tax SavingsSavings CalculatorsBenefit of Spending LessCD (Certificate of Deposit)College SavingsCool Million CalculatorEmergency Savings CalculatorSavings CalculatorSavings GoalsHealth Savings Account (HSA)Personal Finance CalculatorsCheckbook Balancing CalculatorHome Budget AnalysisShould My Spouse Work?Student Budget CalculatorCredit & Debt CalculatorsAccelerated Debt PayoffCredit Card PayoffHome Equity Debt ConsolidationHow Much Do You Owe?Personal Debt ConsolidationRetirement Calculators401(k) Savings401(k) Spend It or Save ItBeneficiary Required Minimum DistributionsRetirement IncomeRetirement Nest EggRetirement PlannerRoth IRATraditional IRAInsurance CalculatorsLife Insurance CalculatorLong Term Care CalculatorPromotionsBlogLocations & HoursContactAboutOur Story & MissionThe Credit Union DifferenceCredit Union AdvocacyMembershipCommunity SupportSupported OrganizationsThe Teacher StoreRequest a DonationCareersCultureBenefitsOpen PositionsNews & EventsNewsletterAnnual ReportBoard of DirectorsCOVID-19 ResponseYour Money is SafeCARES Act Stimulus PaymentsCoronavirus ScamsSmall Business ResourcesSearch
